Eh?
No, it's nothing.
Here we go. First, goo. Janken goo.
We haven't told you what we're shooting for today.
That's the scariest part.
Here's the problem.
Out of the three of us, there's actually one person who knows what we're shooting for and is actually enjoying the fact that the other two are a little scared.
And he's actually enjoying the fact that the other two are a little bit scared.
What's that?
That's probably it, right?
There's one person who's been smiling the whole time.
What?
You know what?
Get out of the car.
Yes, sir! Get out!
Yes, sir.
I'm coming through the arcade right now, and you two are talking like it's nighttime.
It's nighttime, and they're talking about how they can't leave until they see a shooting star.
How did you know?
I'm scared.
It's been about 50 minutes... since we left today.
I just want you to relax.
What do you mean? A shooting star, then.
Shooting stars.
I'm smiling.
The other day, when we went up to the temple, we had a planning meeting.
Yasumori-san whispered something that I thought would be great to shoot.
But when I think about it, I feel really sorry.
It's not that I didn't do it.
But it's a project, so I hope we can have fun while doing it.
I don't remember what I said.
Actually, it wasn't during the planning meeting.
I said it in a whisper on the way home when the camera wasn't rolling.
I told you directly, didn't I?
I can't remember at all.
What? Okay, okay.
Then don't say it again.
Yes, I understand.
Why not? It's the scariest thing I've ever seen.
Why is there a loop here, too?
I'm sure I'll find the answer someday if I keep filming.
So here's the opening.
Enjoy!
Yay!
Congratulations!
So, here we are!
This place is called Hanahoshi Shrine in Sendai.
Now that the weather is getting warmer...
What do you do?
Camping! Camping! Camping!
But it's so hot! Summer!
What do you do when you feel like cooling off?
Let me show you again.
What's going on?
This shrine is famous for its spirit.
That's terrible.
Why did you bring me here? You love it.
But I've never heard of this dazzling shrine.
They say if you pray here, you'll meet the Tatari.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Isn't this crazy?
What's a Tatari? What's the Tatari?
It's called the Tatari shrine.
What? What do we do now? I'm going to get sick.
But we're all the same.
It's like any spiritual place.
There's a cliff at the end of it.
At the bottom of the cliff, white snakes sometimes appear.
If you see it, you'll go crazy.
What?
And there's a well on the way up these stairs.
Sometimes a woman comes out from there.
Or something like that.
That's why I'm trying so hard to make this a very long story.
I wish it would get darker.
Let's go home. Let's go home.
That's what I was thinking.
But when I went up the mountain temple...
I saw what a certain person was doing when he took the stairs.
I personally thought it would be interesting.
I thought, "Let's climb the stairs at the sacred spot.
It's kind of funny, isn't it?
Wouldn't it be a little funny?
No, I really thought so.
But you know what?
Hey, what's the deal?
I thought it might be a little late to try visiting a haunted place.
I thought it was a little too late to go to a haunted place, so I thought it would be better to just go over the stairs.
By the way, in a game, there are losers too, right?
You know, there's a shrine behind you.
If you look to the right, you can see the name "Hanabuchi Shrine".
It says "Hanabuchi Shrine", right?
If you come this way...
There is a lighthouse called Hanabuchi Lighthouse.
You play Glico, climb up, and come back down.
The loser will go to the lighthouse alone and take a selfie.
But...
I'm sorry, I really don't want to do this.
This is really interesting.
By the way, this lighthouse is more famous as a haunted place.
This lighthouse is more famous as a haunted place.
I heard that people go to the lighthouse when they send their ghosts to this place.When they send a liver test here, they'd rather go to the lighthouse.
Well, he's the one who said that.
Get a good shot of this.
Since it's too late for a test of courage...
I was thinking of changing it to "Glico.
That sounds fun.
I don't want to lose.
But now that I've said it.
I have to take responsibility for this project.
I'm going to have to take responsibility for this project.
I'll make sure to do my Glico and pay my respects.
I don't want to be rude.
God is here, after all.
If I'm going to fool around with Glico, I'll have to pay my respects at the end.
I think I have to pay my respects and leave.
The bugs are gathering.
Shall we go?
I'm counting on you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's play rock, paper, scissors.
First, let's play rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors!
Oh, shit!
Seriously?
Oh, no!
Number three.
Here we go.
Goo, rock, paper, scissors!
Wait, that's really bad!
Miyu, you're right!
Keep looking to the right!
Look right!
Oh, you already looked!
Here's an incredibly scary well!
Pow! With love!
Goo!
Ah! Here it comes!
What's "pah"?
Pah!
Pineapple.
Soo!
Yee!
Hoo!
Nah!
Goo!
Yee!
Whoo!
What's this? Why is it coming out?
Is your eye here, too?
Yeah, they're right here.
To the right.
I don't want to see it!
Oh, it's really supposed to be stuck out!
I'll play rock-paper-scissors.
Choke!
Chooky!
Chickolate.
I guess I can avoid the punishment.
I'm Goo rock-paper-scissors Goo
Choki!
It's aiko.
Aiko, right?
Goo!
Oh, you're resting.
What?
Can I have another plate?
Let's eat again.
Nuh-uh.
No, it's nothing.
I'll go. Ambassador Goo, Jangkeun Goo.
Goo, so good.
Maybe he heard you.
Never mind, let's go.
Okay, okay.
Nooooo!!!
By the way, the road we're on now is 200 meters.
We haven't arrived yet.
The lighthouse for the penalty game is 400 meters long.
Oh, you mean it's twice as long?
That's right.
That's a surprise.
Let's keep going.
Why is it so bright?
It's so bright.
You're a Parisian, aren't you?
It's a little gooey at first.
It's like "shoo-shoo-shoo-shoo".
lovey-dovey at first
Wow!
What, what, what, what, really stop it!
It was a really loud foot-long boom-boom!
I've never heard a foot-long buzzing before!
This is the place where we wash our hands.
This place is also very famous.
I was told not to touch it too much.
Oh, I'm not supposed to wash my hands?
Oh no, he said, don't wash your hands!
Well, at first it looks like he's not very good at it.
It's true, this time of year...Certainly this time of year.
How can you be a blur in this situation?
Gourry go.
Ooh.
I didn't do it.
What?
How about we go over here as friends?
Hey, hey, hey.
We're in.
We're on the same team.
Let's start the last round with the chookies.
Chooky.
All right. - All right.
Ready, go.
So, let's get Sapporol.
Okay, what do you think?
Chooky.
Miyu wins.
Miyu.
Choki.
Interesting! The goal has been reached!
Wow!
I got the goal!
Thank God!
Sesiagu Jakepoi
Interesting!
Shiyokoreito
Here it is!
It's aiko, right?
Aiko, right?
We're so close.
Shiyoko koreito!
Goal!
I don't know, but he lost.
It's decided.
It's decided!
Hikarikan has lost!
Yay!
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
How was it? I was the one who came up with the idea.
I'm sorry that my indiscretion
I've caused you all a great deal of pain.
I sincerely apologize.
I'm so sorry.
It's true.
Then let's go home.
Thank you very much.
So after we get off.
Mr. Ite Soumori still has the matter of going to the tower.
I don't know how hard I've been working on this.
I'm doing my very best.
I don't know.
You've worked so hard until now, haven't you?
You did your best.
The other night at Twice
It was a great show.
It was, wasn't it?
With everything you've built up so far...
I'm willing to call it even.
Before coming to the shoot today.
I was listening to the DM before coming to the shoot.
I thought it would cheer me up.
I'm sure these people can do anything.
Let's think about it once we get off the plane.
You're splitting it up.
Since the time of the mountain temple at Oniyama-ji
I already know the way
You're going back way too fast.
Whoa!
You're out of here early!
I thought we'd go a little further first, like normal.
Do you want me to do it again?
Do it again?
Take two, please.
Oh, no!
Action!
What? Miyu...
You were there, weren't you?
Miyu?
I'm sorry, my dog...
Oh, no! I'll put him on.
I'm sorry to disturb you at this time of night.
Say hello to the camera.
Excuse me, sir.
Do that face again.
Stupid face.
Huh!
Take3
I'd like to go up to Hana-Setsu Todai as a penalty game.
But since I'm the organizer of this event, I'll be responsible for taking the best looking selfie.
I'll be there.
I'll be waiting for you.
Bye bye!
I'm coming with you!
Shall we go and talk about scary stories?Would you like to go with a scary story?
They say scary stories make people come to you.
Yes, of course.
What's this? It's a sign.
It's already written in plain English.
"Push over a fall...
Hey, really, really... how can it be that obvious?
It's like a spider's web caught in a bump.
You say, "Oh," right?
I'm glad you saw that... spiderweb.
Yes, it is.
You know everything.
You know as much as I do.
It's a lighthouse, not a shrine.
I'm sure it's well-maintained.
Is that a disadvantage?
I can't help but get suspicious.
I can't do this alone.
It was a close call, wasn't it?
It was pretty serious.
I'm glad I didn't make the most of it.
LOL!
The cameraman said that, so it was really bad.
It's rare to see such a scared Waka.
I think it's rare.
This kind of thing comes out suddenly, doesn't it?
Here it comes.
It doesn't show up on camera at all, but you know what?
There's a bad vibe.
Of course it's not good.
It's really a lighthouse.
It really is a bit...
I don't like it.
It's not good.
It's not cool.
There's a warning here.
Here he comes!
I can't see it on camera, but...
I can't see anything on camera.
I can't see anything.
That's great!
What? Why?
Let's stop.
The staff member said, "Let's stop.
I'm home.
How'd it go?
It's like in a show, you feel like you shouldn't get any closer.
I really experienced that.
I don't want you to do that anymore.
You didn't take any pictures?
I did... good luck.
But you took the second one, and then we're done.
Wow!
I'm so lucky... but you scared me.
You scared me.
You scared me, too.
Bug in the face!
Oh, my God!
I went home.
I'm going to tell you exactly what I just told you.
Sound is air vibration.
So when you clap your hands, the sound resonates through the air.
But if something is there, the sound stops resonating.
So if you feel something is there, you clap your hands.
It is often said that the sound of a clapped hand does not resonate where there is something there.
I'm sure there are times when you stay in a hotel on a tour or something.
When you take a shower, you close your eyes.
You might drop your shampoo in the shower because it's not in your own house.
I thought it's the same reason why it doesn't make a sound when you drop it.
I told her to be careful in the shower.
What do you mean?
Oh, I see.
I won't be able to shower anymore.
I'm going to play dirty.
We're going to do the show without taking a bath.
So that's Part 1.
I did a Glico at a haunted place.
That's a funny title.
Thank you very much.
I hope you enjoy the next video.
Please look forward to the next video.